Xiaoguang Li

Liaoning, China



xiaoguang.dev@hotmail.com



linkedin.com/in/xiaoguang-li-308596223

Summary

Curious, avid learner, relentless debugger, excellent developer with hands on experience in Full-stack development.

Experienced in a variety of languages and systems including but not limited to:

- 1. Back-end Development
- Node.js / Express / Nest / Next
- Python / Django
- Ruby On Rails
- PHP / Laravel / Codeigniter
- 2. Front-end Development
- React.is, React Native
- Angular, Angular.js
- Vue.js
- Web3.js
- 3. Blockchain Development
- Solidity
- Rust
- Hyperledger

Knowledge of Google's Penguin 4.0 algorithm and its updates, ranked over 50+ websites #1 on Google search. Utilizes best practices for optimizing code and adheres to SOLID principles. Self-starter, great with people, responsible, creative, dependable, proficient and timely in completing projects.

Experience

themise Full Stack Developer

themes ninja

Feb 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

ThemesNinja company was building food delivery mobile applications and my role was updating/ maintaining applications.

Key Contributions:

· Maintain released product to be bug-free and more attractive

Full Stack Developer

CoinPanel

Apr 2020 - Apr 2022 (2 years 1 month)

CoinPanel was one of the fast-growing DeFi platform and my main role was building the mobile application using React Native.

The platform was using the trending blockchain technologies including Web3 and Solidity.

Key Contributions:

- · Provide high quality work and advice on blockchain area
- · Extensive knowledge in hybrid tech area
- · Successfully launched mobile application for customers

MAKER Frontend Developer

Yaymaker

Mar 2018 - Feb 2020 (2 years)

Yaymaker was building the Virtual Event Platform and I was responsible in building the front-end of several websites.

I built high-performance, well-structured front-end using React.js/Redux and SCSS.

Key Contributions:

· Built User Friendly/Responsive UI/UX using React.js



Full Stack Developer

Blockchain Terminal (BCT)

Dec 2016 - Jan 2018 (1 year 2 months)

BCT was DeFi plaform and provided the cryptocurrency exchange and trading service. I assisted in developing, executing strategic plans and building products. As a full-stack engineer, I managed both of front-end and back-end and released the first product successfully.

Key Achievements:

- · Deep knowledge in blockchain area
- · Secured application from possible cyber attacks
- · Released the application to the production



Full Stack Developer

resmio GmbH

Feb 2016 - Oct 2016 (9 months)

Resmio is Restaurant Reservation SAAS platform and I began my engineering career from this

As a full-stack developer, I used Python/Django and React to built the platform.

Key Achievements:

- · Remote working Experience
- · Contributed to release the product successfully

Education



University of Science and Technology of China

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Jan 2011 - Dec 2015

Licenses & Certifications

- React Certificate HackerRank bc627417169b
- CSS Certificate HackerRank 9402388ECEF4
- Javascript Certificate HackerRank
 481402E48C54

Skills

Rust (Programming Language) • Node.js • React.js • Solidity • web3.js • React Native • JavaScript • TypeScript • Python (Programming Language) • Ruby on Rails